

SHELBY KOHRING

Bethpage, TN 37022 · 615.426.6948 <u>kohringsw@gmail.com</u> <u>shelbykohring.com</u>

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Applying acquired skills in graphic design and web development to help businesses and organizations better represent themselves online, while also hoping to increase my experience in order to expand positive influence in my community as well as world-wide.

PROJECTS & TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Development Projects

- · Weather Dashboard: <u>GitHub Repository</u> · <u>Deployed Application</u>
- · Simply Plan It: <u>GitHub Repository</u> · <u>Deployed Application</u>
- · Hike Now (Group Project): <u>GitHub Repository</u> · <u>Deployed Application</u>

Full Stack Web Development · Bootcamp Certified 2021

- · Front end: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, with tools such as Bootstrap, Tailwind and jQuery
- · Back end: Experience with Node and Express, as well as MongoDB and MySQL databases

Graphic Design • 10+ years

· Adobe software, specifically fluent in Photoshop and Illustrator; web, email, and print

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

IMPACT Board, Lipscomb University • 2012–Present

- Director of graphics and design, as well as set and stage design, managing teams of 15-20 college students who implement the envisioned plans
- · Designing and incorporating graphics for our program presented to thousands of people each year

Jovenes en Camino · 2019–Present

· Investing in the purpose of a non-profit in Honduras, designing as a volunteer to provide graphics for their website, for email and print distribution, conveying their global impact

Student Ministry • 2008–2021 (McMinnville, TN; Huntsville, AL; Hendersonville, TN)

- Building and strengthening relational skills to better understand how to work with people as a part of multiple teams at three different churches over the last 13 years
- · Developing presentation skills, implementing graphics, design and organization which have helped reach intergenerational audiences, specifically focused on Generation Y & Z

EDUCATION

Vanderbilt University, Coding Bootcamp Certificate • 2020–2021

· Web development and design through Vanderbilt University's Owen Graduate School of Management and School of Engineering

Lipscomb University, Bachelor's Degree in Ministry • 2003–2007

· Ministry and communication to teach and invest in the growth and maturity of adolescents

REFERENCES

Todd Loyd • Director of Content, IMPACT, Lipscomb University: greenlawler@bellsouth.net • 270.725.7245 **Sarah Catherine Teixeira** • Executive Director, Jovenes en Camino: scthetford@gmail.com • 615.545.9238 **Brian Holaway** • Communications, Hendersonville Church: bholaway@hendersonville.org • 615.962.4426